(Leonard:)What happened?
Remember when I auditioned for Rent but
I didn't get it and I couldn't figure out why?
(Sheldon:)I have a conclusion
based on an observation.
(Leonard:)No, you don't.
(Leonard:)No, he doesn't.
The girl picked to play Mimi, she dropped
out and they asked me to replace her.
- Oh! Congratulations, what a lucky break.
- It's not a big deal.
Just one night,
but they invite casting people and agents.
(Penny:)So you never know.
- I think I know.
- No, you don't.
(Leonard:)- He doesn't.
- It's this Friday at 8, you guys wanna come?
(Leonard:)- No.
- No.
Because Friday,
we are attending a symposium...
(Leonard:)...on molecular positronium.
- I think that's a week from Tuesday at 6.
- No, it's this Friday.
- At 8.
- Oh, too bad.
- I gotta get to rehearsal. See you guys.
- See you.
PENNY [SINGING]:
Let's go out tonight
- You just lied to Penny.
- Yes, I did.
(Sheldon:)And you did it so casually.
(Sheldon:)No rapid breathing,
no increase in perspiration.
- So?
- So lack of a physiological response...
(Sheldon:)...while lying
is characteristic of a violent sociopath.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, are you worried
about your safety?
(Sheldon:)No. I imagine if you were going to kill me,
you'd have done it a long time ago.
(Leonard:)That's very true.